nomorebeach.club 2017-12-11

# Privacy & Cookies – No More Beach

At No More Beach, the privacy of visitors and users of the site is hugely important. (Please review [this collection of articles from the Federal Government](http://www.gsa.gov/portal/content/104250 "Federal Law Requires Visitors Be Informed") to learn more about Protecting Privacy.). This privacy policy statement explains the kinds of personal information that is received and collected by No More Beach and how that info is used.

**Quiz Pages**

You can rest assured that the quizzes on this site do not collect any information. If you choose to complete a quiz, your results will be shown to you at the end, but they are NOT collected in any database. No-one else can see your results and as soon as you close the window, they are lost.

Further, we do not collect nor aggregate any statistics about the averages obtained in the completion of the quizzes. As we have stated on their respective pages, they are solely for enjoyment purposes and we want you to have fun.

**Weather and Clock**  
You will notice that the weather information and the clock time zones may show your own region. We do no collect data from these, but rather use your area to compare with the destination that you are traveling to. It is merely a way for you to see the difference between your city and the destination city. Further, the weather and time are derived from a third part source. You may click on those links to determine that company’s privacy policy, as well. 

**Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, No More Beach makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, types of browsers used, Internet Service Providers (ISP), date and time stamps, referring and exiting pages, as well as the number of clicks to analyze trends, maintain the site, track users’ movements in and around the website, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

No More Beach employs cookies: 

  * to store information about visitors’ preferences,
  * to record user-specific information on which pages the user accesses or visits and
  * to customize webpage content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

**DoubleClick DART Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on No More Beach.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to No More Beach and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – <http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>.
  * You may also read [suggested material here](http://www.aboutads.info/ "Google Page Suggestion for Opting Out of Ads") about opting out.

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on No More Beach send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

No More Beach has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. No More Beach‘ privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

[More information is found here from the European Union Commission.](http://ec.europa.eu/ipg/basics/legal/cookies/index_en.htm "EU Description of Cookies")
